# Marcos Henrique Dogo

Custódia Street, 225

Santo André, SP, 09240-140

+55 11 93753-2984

## marcoshdogo@outlook.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/marcoshdogo-2608/

https://github.com/MarkinhosHD

Experience in the IT area a little more than 1 year, performing capture of text using REGEX (Regular Expression) and development of report and component development. I'm not currently last semester of the Systems Analysis and Development course by the UNIFATECIE EAD University Center. I currently work as a self-employed person with deliveries and a driver (UBER).

#### **OBJETIVE**

Trainee in JAVA programming

Trainee Front End

#### **PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE**

# Grifon Brasil Assessoria Ltda. EPP. São Paulo — Administrative Assistant.

MARCH 2016 - JULY 2016

Working with Text Capture from the Official Gazettes of all over Brazil, using Regular Expression;

## Grifon Brasil Assessoria Ltda. EPP. São Paulo — Intern

OCTOBER 2015 - MARCH 2016

Performing Text Capture using Regular Expression;

# Mahler Tecnologia em Internet LTDA – EPP. São Paulo — Intern

SEPTEMBER 2014 - MARCH 2015

- Parameterization of the Gr5 System.
- Report Development.
- Component Development Language used "PostgreSQL".

## **ACADEMIC BACKGROUND:**

## **UniFatecie University Center** — *Analysis and Systems* Development

Studying the last semester of Systems Analysis and Development online.

START IN JANUARY 2021 - END IN JULY 2023

#### **HARD SKILLS**

## **Back End Training** — *Idev* Treinamentos Online

JAVA OOP - Beginning on 25/2022 and completed on 26/2022

## **GIT/GITHUB Trainind** — *Dev* Superior (YouTube Nélio Alves)

Versioning Basic Course - Complete.

## SQL Server 2019 — Alura Ensino Online

3 training courses - Beginning on 27/2022 in progress.

- SQL SERVER
- MvSOL
- RELATIONAL DATABASE MODELING -Conceptual, Logical and Physical

## **Formação Front End** — B7WEB

5 training courses - Beginning on 05/2023 in progress.

- HTML5
- CSS3